

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Mobile App Development Web Development Game Development Ruby programming language C++ programming language

PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative spirit
Reliable and professional
Organized
Time management
Team player
Fast learner
Motivated

INTERESTS

Photography
Music (EDM/Instrumental)
Cinema
Travelling
Exploring Cuisines
Linux command Line

CONTACT

P: +91 9880808152/ +91 7619488873 E: jaseemabdul20@gmail.com W:www.jaseemabdul12.wixsite.com/ mysite

ABDUL JASEEM C K

APP DEVELOPER

ABOUT

I'm an Android Developer, passionate about building great apps. For me app development is not just about coding, it's also about creating an awesome user experience. I'm also a passionate learner when it comes to learning new programming languages and exploring different areas such as web development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

APP DEVELOPER

CMR University| Jan 2018 - Feb 2018

• Developed a News App capable of retrieving and displaying News data from a Firebase database.

APP DEVELOPER

App.Labs | Aug 2019 - Oct 2019

- Developed a Social Media App much like popular platforms such as Instagram with the use of Firebase Cloud Functionality, from scratch.
- Implemented a comfortable User Experience

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT INTERN

Suphalaam Technologies | Jan 2020 - April 2020

- Developed webpages as per company requirements
- Improved on the existing applications and released them on Google Play store
- Added new features and fixing bugs.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATION (GAME AND MOBILE APP DEVELOPMENT

CMR University, 2017-2020

TOOLS

- VS Code
- Android Studio
- XCode
- Unity
- Unreal Engine
- Git
- Slack
- Slac
- TrelloFigma
- Photoshop
- t Cocos2dx